Mercury Press Records
Mercury Press Records
- Manuscripts (Part I)
  - Young, Robert F.
    - Cosmic Caper, Sept 1957; article (Box 38)
    - Dialogue In a Twenty-First Century Dining Room, Feb. 1965; article (Box 38)
    - The Eternal Lovers, Dec. 1963; article (Box 38)
    - Hopsoil, Jan. 1961; article (Box 38)
    - Minutes of a Meeting at the Mitre, undated; article (Box 38)
    - Nikita Eisenhower Jones, Aug. 1960; article (Box 38)
    - Production Problem, Jan. 1959; article (Box 38)
    - Romance in an Eleventh Century Recharging Station, May 1965; article (Box 38)
    - Romance in a Twenty-First Century Used Car Lot, Nov. 1960; article (Box 38)
    - The Second Philadelphia Experiment, July 1964; article (Box 38)
    - Storm Over Sodom, Feb. 1961; article (Box 39)
    - There Was an Old Woman Who Lived in a Shoe, Dec. 1962; article (Box 39)
    - Thirty Days Had September, Oct. 1957; article (Box 39)
    - Your Ghost Will Walk, July 1957; article (Box 39)
    - In What Cavern of the Deep, Oct. 1964; article (Box 39)
    - Jonathan and the Space Whale, March 1962; article (Box 39)
    - L'Arc De Jeanne, Jan. 1966; article (Box 39)
    - To Fell a Tree, July 1959; article (Box 39)
  - Zangwill, Israel
    - Satan Mekatrig (xerox), 1963; article (Box 39)
  - Zelazny, Roger
    - The Doors of His Face, The Lamps of His Mouth, March 1965; article (Box 39)
    - Of Time and the Yan, June 1965; article (Box 39)
    - The Salvation of Faust, May 1964; article (Box 39)
    - This Moment of the Storm, 1966; Jan, article (Box 39)
    - ...And Call Me Conrad (Parts I, II), 1965, Oct. - Nov., book (Box 39)
    - A Rose For Ecclesiastes, Feb. 1963; book (Box 39)
  - Author Unknown
    - The Figgerin' of Aunt Wilma (photo copy), undated; article (Box 39)
    - To The Stars, Dec., 1963; poem (published in the San Francisco Review, Dec., 1965) (Box 39)
- Published material (Part I)
  All printed material has been transferred to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to to locate these items.
  - Boucher, Anthony, ed.
    - The Best From Fantasy and Science Fiction, New York, Ace Books, Sixth Series, 1957, Eighth Series, 1959; book
  - Davidson, Avram, ed.
    - The Best From Fantasy and Science Fiction, New York, Ace Books, 1963; 1964; Twelfth Series, Thirteenth Series
    - The Best from Fantasy and Science Fiction, London, Panther Books Ltd., 1963; Twelfth Series
  - Ferman, Edward L., ed.
    - The Best from Fantasy and Science Fiction, New York Doubleday and Co., 1966; 1967; Fifteenth Series, Sixteenth Series
  - Ferman, Joseph, W., ed.
    - No Limits, New York, Ballantine Books, 1964
  - Mills, Robert P., ed.
    - The Best From Fantasy and Science Fiction, New York, Ace Books, 1959; 1961,; 1962; Ninth Series, Tenth Series, 11th Series
    - The Best From Fantasy and Science Fiction, London, Panther Books Ltd., 1959; Ninth Series
    - A Decade of Fantasy and Science Fiction, New York, Doubleday and Co., 1960
  - Venture
    - No's 2-4, 1963, October-December
    - No's 5-7, 9-14, 16, 1964, January- March; May-October,; December
    - No's 27, 28, 1965, November-December
  - Minotauro
    - No's 1, 2, 1964, September-December
    - No's 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 1965, January-October
    - No. 8, 1966, May-June
  - Venture
    - Vol 1, No's 1-6, 1957
    - Vol. 2, No's 1-4, 1958
  - Fantasy and Science Fiction
    - Vol. 26, No's 1-6, 1964, January-June
    - Vol. 27, No's 1-6, 1964, July-December
    - Vol. 28, No's 1-6, 1965, January-June
    - Vol. 29, No's 1-6, 1965, July-December
    - Vol. 30, No's 1-6, 1966, January-June
    - Vol. 31, No's 1-6, 1966, July-December
- Subject file (Part I)
  - Davidson, Avram, editorials
    - April 1962 (Box 40)
    - Undated (Box 40)
  - White, Ted, undated; editorial (Box 40)
  - Indexes and tables of contents, 1960-1966 (Box 40)
  - Magazine covers, 1949-1959 (Box 40)
  - Magazine covers, 1960-1967 (Box 40)
  - Miscellaneous, dates incomplete (Box 40)
- Correspondence (Part II)
  - Fan mail
    - Miscellaneous, 1949-1956; 11 folders (Box 41)
  - Incoming
    - Unidentified, 1949-1957; undated (Box 41)
    - Aan - Ads, 1949-1958 (Box 41)
    - Aff - Alt, 1949-1958 (Box 41)
    - Ame - Apo, 1951-1956 (Box 41)
    - App - Aye, 1949-1958 (Box 41)
    - Abernathy, Robert, 1953-1957 (Box 42)
    - Ackerman, Forrest J. (L.A.), 1949-1963; 6 folders (Box 42)
    - Altshuler, Harry (L.A.), 1949-1956; 8 folders (Box 42)
    - Anderson, Poul, 1950-1957 (Box 42)
    - Angoff, Charles (L.A.), 1951-1954 (Box 42)
    - Anvil, Chris (Harry Crosby), 1951-1956 (Box 42)
    - Arr, Stephen (Stephen A. Rynas), 1953-1957 (Box 42)
    - Arthur, Robert, 1949-1959 (Box 42)
    - Asimov, Isaac, 1951-1958; 1968; 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Avallone, Michael, 1949-1956 (Box 43)
    - Bab - Ban, 1951-1958 (Box 43)
    - Bar - Ben, 1949-1957 (Box 43)
    - Ber - Blu, 1949-1957 (Box 43)
    - Bog - Boy, 1949-1958 (Box 43)
    - Brac - Brau, 1950-1957 (Box 43)
    - Bre - Bro, 1949-1958 (Box 43)
    - Bud - Byr, 1949-1958 (Box 43)
    - Barr, Stephen, 1953-1958 (Box 43)
    - Beagle, Peter S., 1956; undated (Box 43)
    - Beaumont, Charles, 1953-1957 (Box 43)
    - Beck, Calvin Thomas, 1949-1955; undated (Box 43)
    - Benet, William Rose, 28 Oct 1949 (Box 43)
    - Bester, Alfred, 1950-1956; 3 folders (Box 43)
    - Bigelow, Leslie, 1950-1954 (Box 43)
    - Binder, Otto, 1952-1957; undated (Box 43)
    - Blassingame, Lurton (L.A.), 1951-1958; undated (Box 43)
    - Blish, James, 1952-1958 (Box 43)
    - Bloch, Robert, 1952-1961; undated (Box 43)
    - Boardman, John, 1953-1957 (Box 44)
    - Bond, Nelson, 1950-1956 (Box 44)
    - Bonestell, Chesley, 1950-1956 (Box 44)
    - Brackett, Leigh, 1953-1957 (Box 44)
    - Bradbury, Ray, 1949-1956 (Box 44)
    - Bradley, Marion Z., 1950-1957 (Box 44)
    - Bretnor, Reginald, 1949-1958 (Box 44)
    - Brookbank, Richard, 1949-1958 (Box 44)
    - Brown, Bill, 1950-1956 (Box 44)
    - Brown, Frederic, 1949-1956 (Box 44)
    - Brown, James Oliver (L.A.), 1949-1957 (Box 44)
    - Brandt & Brandt (L.A.), 1949-1958 (Box 44)
    - Buck, Doris P., 1951-1959 (Box 44)
    - Cab - Cap, 1949-1957 (Box 44)
    - Card - Carl, 1952-1958 (Box 44)
    - Carm - Carr, 1950-1957 (Box 44)
    - Cars - Cass, 1950-1957 (Box 44)
    - Cast - Chan, 1946-1957 (Box 44)
    - Chap - Char, 1950-1958 (Box 44)
    - Chas - Cic, 1948-1958 (Box 44)
    - Cla - Cli, 1949-1956 (Box 44)
    - Clo - Cok, 1949-1957 (Box 44)
    - Col - Con, 1949-1957 (Box 44)
    - Cook - Coop, 1950-1957 (Box 44)
    - Cor - Cox, 1949-1956 (Box 44)
    - Crab - Cran, 1950-1956 (Box 44)
    - Craw - Cut, 1949-1958 (Box 44)
    - Caravan, T. D. (Charles Munoz), 1951-1952 (Box 45)
    - Carlson, Esther, 1952-1953 (Box 45)
    - Carter, Manfred, 1949-1950 (Box 45)
    - Carter, Paul, 1949-1957 (Box 45)
    - Cartmill, Cleve, 1946-1955 (Box 45)
    - Cassens, Kenneth H., 1949-1958 (Box 45)
    - Clarke, Arthur C., 1951-1956 (Box 45)
    - Clement, Hal (Harry C. Stubbs), 1954-1956 (Box 45)
    - Clingerman, Mildred, 1951-1958 (Box 45)
    - Coblentz, Stanton A., 1949-1957 (Box 45)
    - Coffin, Carlyn, 1949-1958 (Box 45)
    - Cogswell, Theodore, 1953-1958 (Box 45)
    - Cole, Les (John Collier), 1951-1958 (Box 45)
    - Coppel, Alfred J., 1950-1956 (Box 45)
    - Crackel, Jay T., 1950-1958 (Box 45)
    - Crossen, Kendell, 1950-1953 (Box 45)
    - Curtis, Betsy, 1949-1955 (Box 45)
    - Curtis Brown Ltd. (L.A.), 1949-1958 (Box 45)
    - Dag - Dar, 1946-1957 (Box 45)
    - Dav - Del, 1949-1958 (Box 45)
    - Dem - Dew, 1949-1956 (Box 45)
    - Dic - Dye, 1950-1958 (Box 45)
    - Dance, Dr. C.L., Jr., 1950-1955 (Box 45)
    - Davidson, Avram A., 1950-1958 (Box 45)
    - DeAngelis, Guy, 1952-1962 (Box 45)
    - deCamp, L. Sprague, 1949-1957 (Box 45)
    - deFord, Miriam Allen, 1949-1960 (Box 45)
    - Derleth, August, 1949-1957 (Box 45)
    - Dick, Philip K., 1951-1954 (Box 45)
    - Dickson, Gordon R., 1950-1958 (Box 45)
    - DiRienzo, Constance, 1950-1957 (Box 46)
    - Doubleday & Company, 1951-1958 (Box 46)
    - Drake, Leah Bodine, 1951-1957 (Box 46)
    - Drussai, Garen, 1951-1960 (Box 46)
    - Ear - Eyn, 1949-1958 (Box 46)
    - Edmondson, G. C., 1955-1958 (Box 46)
    - Elliott, George P., 1950-1957 (Box 46)
    - Elmo, Ann (L.A.), 1951-1958 (Box 46)
    - Fab - Flu, 1949-1957 (Box 46)
    - Foo - Fur, 1949-1957 (Box 46)
    - Farmer, Philip Jose, 1951-1958 (Box 46)
    - Ferman, Joseph W.
      - 1946-1953, 5 folders (Box 46)
      - 1954-1958, 4 folders (Box 47)
    - Finney, Jack, 1949-1957 (Box 47)
    - Fles, Bartold (L.A.), 1950-1958 (Box 47)
    - Flood, Les (L.A.), 1951-1957 (Box 47)
    - Fontenay, Charles, 1951-1957 (Box 47)
    - Fyfe, Horace B., 1949-1956 (Box 47)
    - Gaf - Gau, 1950-1956 (Box 47)
    - Gel - Glu, 1949-1958 (Box 47)
    - God - Gou, 1949-1958 (Box 47)
    - Gra - Gre, 1949-1954 (Box 47)
    - Gri - Gus, 1949-1956 (Box 47)
    - Galouie, Daniel F., 1953-1956 (Box 47)
    - Gardiner, Martin, 1949-1957; 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Gilbert, Doris, 1951-1954 (Box 47)
    - Gold, Horace, 1950-1954 (Box 47)
    - Gregory & Fitch (L.A.), 1949-1957 (Box 47)
    - Grimes, Lee, 1950-1956 (Box 47)
    - Haa - Ham, 1949-1956 (Box 48)
    - Han - Haz, 1949-1957 (Box 48)
    - Hea - Hir, 1949-1957 (Box 48)
    - Hoc - Hyn, 1949-1958 (Box 48)
    - Heinlein, Robert, 1950-1958 (Box 48)
    - Henderson, Zenna, 1950-1958 (Box 48)
    - Hoffman, Lee, 1954-1956.; undated (Box 48)
    - Horch, Franz J. (L.A.), 1950-1954 (Box 48)
    - Iam - Irw, 1950-1956 (Box 48)
    - Jac - Joh, 1949-1958 (Box 48)
    - Jon - Jul, 1949-1958 (Box 48)
    - Joseph, Nannine, 1955-1957 (Box 48)
    - Kaa - Kin, 1949-1959 (Box 48)
    - Kir - Kut, 1949-1958 (Box 48)
    - Kelly, Dan, 1949-1955 (Box 48)
    - Kline, Otis, Associates (L.A.), 1949-1958 (Box 48)
    - Knight, Damon, 1949-1957 (Box 48)
    - Kornbluth, Cyril, 1955-1958 (Box 48)
    - Lab - Ley, 1949-1958 (Box 48)
    - Lib - Lyo, 1949-1957 (Box 48)
    - Lang, Allen Kim, 1949-1957 (Box 48)
    - Lewis, C. S., 1957 (Box 48)
    - Littauer & Wilkinson (L.A.), 1951-1958 (Box 48)
    - Little Brown & Company, 1951-1953 (Box 49)
    - Ludwig, Edward, 1950-1955 (Box 49)
    - Lupoff, Richard, 1952 (Box 49)
    - McA - McN, 1946-1958 (Box 49)
    - Mad - Met, 1949-1958 (Box 49)
    - Mic - Min, 1949-1958 (Box 49)
    - Mof - Mow, 1949-1964 (Box 49)
    - Muc - Mye, 1949-1958 (Box 49)
    - M. C. A. Management, Ltd. (L.A.), 1951-1958 (Box 49)
    - McClintic, Winona (Mrs. William Martin), undated; 1950-1958 (Box 49)
    - M'Intosh (McIntosh), J. T. (James Macgregor), 1952-1956 (Box 49)
    - McKeogh, Elsie (L.A.), 1950-1955 (Box 49)
    - Marsh, Willard, 1953-1958 (Box 49)
    - Matheson, Richard, 1949-1958 (Box 49)
    - Matson, Harold (L.A.), 1950-1958 (Box 49)
    - Mavis McIntosh, Mckee & Batchelder (L.A.), 1950-1957 (Box 49)
    - Meredith, Scott, 1949-1958; undated; 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Merril, Judith, 1951-1958 (Box 49)
    - Merwin, Sam, Jr., 1950-1953 (Box 49)
    - Miller, P. Schuyler, 1949-1957 (Box 50)
    - Miller, Walter M., 1950-1957 (Box 50)
    - Mills, Bob, 1949-1958; undated; 10 folders (Box 50)
    - Moore, Ward, 1949-1958; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Morrison, William (Joseph Samachson), 1950-1958 (Box 51)
    - Nab - Ney, 1950-1957 (Box 51)
    - Nib - Nyb, 1950-1965 (Box 51)
    - Nearing, H., Jr., 1950-1955 (Box 51)
    - Nelson, Alan, 1950-1954 (Box 51)
    - Neville, Kris, 1950-1957; undated (Box 51)
    - Nolan, William, 1952-1957 (Box 51)
    - Norton, Andre (Mary Alice Norton), 1953-1958 (Box 51)
    - Nourse, Alan E., 1951-1957 (Box 51)
    - Oak - Oli, 1950-1955 (Box 51)
    - Ols - Owe, 1950-1958 (Box 51)
    - Oliver, Chad, 1950-1957 (Box 51)
    - Oliver, J. T., 1950-1952 (Box 51)
    - Pac - Pay, 1949-1958 (Box 51)
    - Pea - Phi, 1949-1958 (Box 51)
    - Pie - Pow, 1949-1958 (Box 51)
    - Pra - Put, 1949-1958 (Box 51)
    - Palmer, Stuart, 1946-1958 (Box 52)
    - Phelan, Jeremiah (C. Daly King), 1950-1951 (Box 52)
    - Phillips, Roger (Roger P. Graham), 1952-1958 (Box 52)
    - Pierce, John R., 1949-1956 (Box 52)
    - Pohl, Frederik, 1949-1957; 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Porges, Arthur, 1950-1957; 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Pratt, Fletcher, 1949-1954 (Box 52)
    - Pruyn, Howard K., 1950-1956 (Box 52)
    - Qua - Qui, 1949-1957 (Box 52)
    - Quick, Dorothy, 1950-1960 (Box 52)
    - Rab - Ree, 1949-1958 (Box 52)
    - Reg - Riv, 1949-1958 (Box 52)
    - Roa - Rog, 1949-1958 (Box 52)
    - Roh - Roz, 1949-1958 (Box 52)
    - Rub - Ryk, 1950-1958 (Box 52)
    - Ready, William B., 1951-1956 (Box 53)
    - Reed, Kit, 1956-1960 (Box 53)
    - Reynolds, Mack, 1951-1957 (Box 53)
    - Reynolds & Son, Paul R. (L.A.), 1946-1957 (Box 53)
    - Roberts, Jane (Mrs. Robert Butts), 1954-1957 (Box 53)
    - Robin, Ralph, 1949-1957 (Box 53)
    - Rodell, Marie F. (L.A.), 1948-1957 (Box 53)
    - Rogers, Kay, 1950-1957 (Box 53)
    - Russell, Ray, 1954-1958 (Box 53)
    - Saa - Sal, 1949-1956 (Box 53)
    - Sam - San, 1949-1957 (Box 53)
    - Sap - Sax, 1949-1958 (Box 53)
    - Scha - Schi, 1949-1957 (Box 53)
    - Schl - Schw, 1950-1958 (Box 53)
    - Sci - Scr, 1951-1957 (Box 53)
    - Sec - Sey, 1951-1957 (Box 53)
    - Shaa - Shaw, 1949-1957 (Box 53)
    - She - Shy, 1949-1957 (Box 53)
    - Sib - Sil, 1950-1958 (Box 53)
    - Sim - Sit, 1950-1958 (Box 53)
    - Ske - Sma, 1950-1957 (Box 53)
    - Smi - Sny, 1949-1963 (Box 53)
    - Sob - Sow, 1950-1958 (Box 53)
    - Spa - Squ, 1949-1957 (Box 53)
    - Stag - Stat, 1949-1957 (Box 54)
    - Stea - Stew, 1949-1958 (Box 54)
    - Sti - Sto, 1950-1957 (Box 54)
    - Str - Stu, 1949-1957 (Box 54)
    - Sul - Sut, 1949-1958 (Box 54)
    - Swa - Szu, 1950-1957 (Box 54)
    - St. Clair, Eric (Idris Seabright - Wife), 1952-1957 (Box 54)
      See also his wife, Seabright, Idris (Margaret St. Clair).
    - Sanders, Sidney A. (L.A.), 1949-1955 (Box 54)
    - Saunders, Marion (L.A.), 1950-1957 (Box 54)
    - Schaffner, John (L.A.), 1949-1957; 2 folders (Box 54)
    - Schoenfeld, Howard, 1949-1957 (Box 54)
    - Seabright, Idris (Margaret St. Clair), 1950-1958 (Box 54)
      See also her husband, St. Clair, Eric.
    - Shaw Associates, Joseph T. (L.A.), 1951-1952 (Box 54)
    - Silverberg, Robert, 1955-1958 (Box 54)
    - Simak, Clifford, 1951-1957 (Box 54)
    - Sinclair, Upton, 1953-1955 (Box 54)
    - Smith, Evelyn, 1951-1956 (Box 54)
    - Smith, Ron, 1955-1957 (Box 54)
    - Spivak, Lawrence, 1946-1954 (Box 54)
    - Stanton, Will, 1950-1957 (Box 54)
    - Starin, Florence (L.A.), 1951-1956 (Box 54)
    - Sternig, Larry (L.A.), 1950-1957 (Box 54)
    - Sturgeon, Theodore, 1949-1956 (Box 54)
    - Taa - Tay, 1950-1958 (Box 54)
    - Tea - Thu, 1949-1958 (Box 54)
    - Tib - Tow, 1949-1958 (Box 54)
    - Tra - Tsv, 1949-1957 (Box 54)
    - Tub - Tyr, 1949-1957 (Box 54)
    - Taylor, Graves, 1949-1952 (Box 55)
    - Tenn, William (Philip Klass), 1949-1955 (Box 55)
    - Terrill, Rogers (L.A.), 1953-1957 (Box 55)
    - Tucker, Wilson (Bob), 1949-1958 (Box 55)
    - Twayne Publishers, Inc., 1952-1955 (Box 55)
    - Uhl - Uy, 1950-1957 (Box 55)
    - Vac - Vel, 1949-1958 (Box 55)
    - Ven - Vuj, 1950-1958 (Box 55)
    - Vidal, Gore, 1 May 1957 (Box 55)
    - Wac - Wal, 1950-1957 (Box 55)
    - Wan - Way, 1949-1958 (Box 55)
    - Wea - Wex, 1949-1957 (Box 55)
    - Wha - Whi, 1950-1958 (Box 55)
    - Wic - Wit, 1949-1957 (Box 55)
    - Wla - Wor, 1950-1957 (Box 55)
    - Wra - Wrz, 1950-1958 (Box 55)
    - Wub - Wys, 1950-1957 (Box 55)
    - Wainwright, Ruth L., 1950-1958 (Box 55)
    - Wallace, Irving, 1952-1958 (Box 55)
    - Webb, Charles T., 1952-1956 (Box 55)
    - Wellman, Manly Wade, 1949-1958 (Box 55)
    - White, Kenneth S. (L.A.), 1953-1956 (Box 55)
    - Williams, Robert M., 1952-1957 (Box 55)
    - Willis Kingsley Wing (L.A.), 1949-1957 (Box 55)
    - Wilson, Richard, 1952-1957 (Box 55)
    - Wolf, Harriet (L.A.), 1952-1956 (Box 56)
    - Wolf, Leonard, 1951-1954 (Box 56)
    - Wood, Christopher, 1949-1953 (Box 56)
    - Wyndham, John (John Harris), 1951-1952 (Box 56)
    - Yac - Yur, 1950-1958 (Box 56)
    - Young, Robert F., 1953-1957 (Box 56)
    - Zab - Zwi, 1949-1957 (Box 56)
  - Outgoing
    - Undated, 2 folders (Box 56)
    - 1946, Mar - Jul (Box 56)
    - 1949, Mar - Dec, 5 folders (Box 56)
    - 1950, Jan - Apr, 5 folders (Box 56)
    - 1950, May - Dec, 9 folders (Box 57)
    - 1951, Jan - Jun, 6 folders (Box 57)
    - 1951, Jul - Dec, 6 folders (Box 58)
    - 1952, Jan - Jun, 7 folders (Box 58)
    - 1952, Jul - Dec, 5 folders (Box 59)
    - 1953, Jan - Jun, 6 folders (Box 59)
    - 1953, Jul - Dec, 6 folders (Box 60)
    - 1954, Jan - Aug, 8 folders (Box 60)
    - 1954, Sep - Dec, 4 folders (Box 61)
    - 1955, Jan - Dec, 10 folders (Box 61)
    - 1956, Jan - Feb, 2 folders (Box 61)
    - 1956, Mar - Dec, 10 folders (Box 62)
    - 1957, Jan - Aug, 8 folders (Box 62)
    - 1957, Sep - Dec, 4 folders (Box 63)
    - 1958, Jan - Sep, 4 folders (Box 63)
    - 1959, Jan - Aug (Box 63)
    - 1961, Mar (Box 63)
- Fantasy and Science Fiction (Part II)
  - Editorial records
    - Blurbs (author), undated (Box 63)
    - Clippings, 1949-1958; undated; 10 folders (Box 63)
    - Literary manuscripts
      - Fragments (Box 63)
      - Index file of contributing authors (Box 64)
      - Indexes, vol. 34 & 35, 1968 (Box 65)
      - Unidentified authors (Box 65)
      - Aandahl, Vance
        - "Beyond the Game", May 1968 (Box 65)
        - "Drool", Feb 1969 (Box 65)
      - Abeel, William C.
        - "The Beast of Mouryessa", May 1969 (Box 65)
      - Abernathy, Robert
        - "Axolotl", Jan 1954 (Box 65)
        - "The Fishers", Dec 1954 (Box 65)
        - "Heirs Apparent", Jun 1954 (Box 65)
      - Adams, Raymond J.
        - "The Newcomers", undated (Box 65)
      - Adcock, George
        - Untitled, 30 Nov 1957 (Box 65)
      - Agnew, Bruce A.
        - "The Key", Jun 1953 (Box 65)
      - Alden, Theodora
        - "Nightcapade", 17 Apr 1956 (Box 65)
      - Alden, W. L.
        - "Van Wagener's Ways", undated (Box 65)
      - Aldiss, Brian W.
        - "Randy's Syndrome", Apr 1967 (Box 65)
      - Amos, Charles Carol
        - "Space Flight", 5 Oct 1956 (Box 65)
      - Anderson, Poul
        - "The Immortal Game", 13 Apr 1953 (Box 65)
        - "Inside Straight", Aug 1955 (Box 65)
        - "Interloper", Apr 1951 (Box 65)
        - "Operation Changeling" (Part I), May 1969 (Box 65)
        - "Operation Changeling" (Part II), Jun 1969 (Box 65)
        - "Three Hearts and Three Lions", Sep 1953 (Box 65)
        - "Three Hearts and Three Lions" (con), 1953, Oct (Box 65)
        - Untitled, undated (Box 65)
      - Anderson, Poul and Dickson, Gordon R.
        - "The Tiddlywink Warriors", Aug 1955 (Box 65)
      - Angell, Roger
        - "Just a Matter of Time", 1950, Fall (Box 65)
      - Anthony, John
        - "The Bone That Seeks", Mar 1955 (Box 65)
        - "The Hypnoglyph", Jul 1953 (Box 65)
      - Anthony, Piers
        - "Sos the Rope", Aug 1968 (Box 65)
      - Apollinaire, Guillaume
        - "Remote Projection", Jul 1968 (Box 65)
      - Appleman, Evan H.
        - "'Twas Brillig...", Jun 1951 (Box 65)
      - Armstrong, Charlotte
        - "Three Day Magic", Sep 1952 (Box 65)
      - Arr, Stephen
        - "Cause", Aug 1955 (Box 65)
      - Arthur, Chet
        - "The Lucky People", Feb 1968 (Box 65)
      - Arthur, Robert
        - "Postpaid to Paradise", 1950, Winter (Box 65)
        - "Wilfred Weem, Dreamer", Aug 1951 (Box 65)
      - Ashby, Richard
        - "The Sling", Aug 1952 (Box 66)
      - Asimov, Isaac
        - "The Fateful Lightning", Jun 1969 (Box 66)
        - "Flies", Jun 1953 (Box 66)
        - "Key Item", Jul 1968 (Box 66)
        - "Science", 1967, Jan - May 1969; 10 folders (Box 66)
        - "Segregationist", Oct 1968 (Box 66)
        - "The Talking Stone", Oct 1955 (Box 66)
      - Bailey, Hilary
        - "The Little Victims", Nov 1967 (Box 66)
      - Ballard, J. G.
        - "The Cloud-Sculptors of Coral D", Dec 1967 (Box 66)
        - "Cry Hope, Cry Fury", Oct 1967 (Box 66)
        - "The Sublimation World", Jul 1968 (Box 66)
      - Barnett, C. A.
        - "A Tale to Tell", Apr 1952 (Box 66)
      - Barr, Robert
        - "The Doom of London", Jun 1954 (Box 66)
      - Barr, Stephen
        - "The Evaporation of Jugby", Sep 1968 (Box 66)
        - "Miss Van Winkle", Dec 1968 (Box 66)
      - Barry, Jerome
        - "The Milk of Paradise", Dec 1953 (Box 66)
      - Basch, Joan Patricia
        - "Alas Poor Yorick! I Knew Him Well Enuff", Sep 1967 (Box 66)
      - Beaumont, Charles
        - "Gentlemen be Seated", Jun 1967 (Box 66)
        - "The Quadrioptican", Aug 1954 (Box 66)
        - "The Science Screen", Dec 1955 (Box 66)
      - Benford, Grey
        - "Deeper Than the Darkness", Apr 1969 (Box 67)
      - Bennett, Kem
        - "Rufus", Feb 1956 (Box 67)
      - Bennett, Margot
        - "An Old Fashioned Poker for My Uncle's Head", May 1954 (Box 67)
      - Bester, Alfred
        - "5,271,009", Mar 1954 (Box 67)
        - "Hobson's Choice", Aug 1952 (Box 67)
        - "Of Time and Third Avenue", Oct 1951 (Box 67)
        - "Star Light, Star Bright", Jul 1953 (Box 67)
        - "Time is the Traitor", Sep 1953 (Box 67)
      - Biese, L. J. T.
        - "The Baron's Dog", Aug 1967 (Box 67)
      - Bigelow, Leslie
        - "The Sorcerer's Apprentice", Mar 1953 (Box 67)
      - Biggle, Lloyd, Jr.
        - "In His Own Image", Jan 1968 (Box 67)
      - Binder, Eando
        - "A Warning to the Furious", Aug 1953 (Box 67)
      - Birkin, Charles
        - "Ballet Nêgre", Nov 1967 (Box 67)
      - Blanchard, Jack
        - "Underneath the Bough", undated (Box 67)
      - Blish, James
        - "First Strike", Jun 1953 (Box 67)
      - Boucher, Anthony
        - "The First", Oct 1952 (Box 67)
        - "Recommended Reading", 1950, Summer - Apr 1956; undated; 6 folders (Box 67)
        - "The Science Fiction Editor", undated (Box 67)
        - "Snulbug", May 1953 (Box 67)
      - Bova, Ben
        - "Fifteen Miles", May 1967 (Box 67)
      - Bowen, Elizabeth
        - "The Cheery Soul", Apr 1952 (Box 67)
      - Bradbury, Ray
        - "All Summer In a Day", Mar 1954 (Box 67)
        - "The Dragon", Mar 1956 (Box 67)
        - "The Exiles", 1950, Winter (Box 67)
        - "The Pedestrian", Feb 1952 (Box 67)
        - "The Wilderness", Nov 1952 (Box 67)
      - Bradley, Marion Zimmer
        - "The Climbing Wave", Feb 1955 (Box 68)
      - Bragg, R.
        - "Lyra", undated (Box 68)
      - Breed, Eleanor
        - "The Escapist", 12 Aug 1952 (Box 68)
        - "This Planet", 12 Aug 1952 (Box 68)
      - Bretnor, R.
        - "Earthwoman", Aug 1967 (Box 68)
        - "The Gnurrs Come From the Woodwork Out", 1950, Winter (Box 68)
        - "Maybe Just a Little One", Feb 1953 (Box 68)
        - "Mrs. Poppledore's ID", Feb 1952 (Box 68)
        - "One of the Family", Feb 1951 (Box 68)
        - "Party Night", Mar 1969 (Box 68)
      - Briarton, Grendel
        - "Through Time and Space With Ferdinand Feghoot", undated (Box 68)
        - "Through Time and Space With Ferdinand Feghoot", May 1956 (Box 68)
      - Brode, Anthony
        - "Flying Chaucer", Mar 1956 (Box 68)
        - "The Watchers", 28 Jan 1957 (Box 68)
        - "Yes, But...", 28 Jan 1957 (Box 68)
      - Brody, Larry
        - "Demon", Apr 1968 (Box 68)
        - "Nightwalker", Feb 1969 (Box 68)
        - "Ultimate Defense", Jul 1968 (Box 68)
      - Brookbank, Richard
        - "The Cocoon", Oct 1951 (Box 68)
        - "The Invisible Wall", Aug 1954 (Box 68)
      - Broughton, Rhoda
        - "The Man With the Nose", Oct 1954 (Box 68)
      - Brown, Bill
        - "Spunk Water", Mar 1954 (Box 68)
        - "The Star Ducks", 1950, Fall (Box 68)
        - "The Tronk and the Trumpet", Oct 1953 (Box 68)
      - Brown, Frederic
        - "Rustle of Wings", Aug 1953 (Box 68)
      - Browne, Tom